[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Near what sea was the ancient city of Troy located ?", "correct_answer": "Aegean", "incorrect_answers": ["Mediterranean", "Ionian", "Adriatic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What geographical region are chinchillas native to?", "correct_answer": "South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "Africa", "North America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these dinosaurs had dorsal plates and spikes?", "correct_answer": "Stegosaurus", "incorrect_answers": ["Heloderma  suspectum", "H. horridum", "Hydrodamalis gigans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cornea of the eye is the transparent front part that covers the iris, pupil, and anterior chamber. Which of these statements is true about the cornea?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The cornea does not have blood vessels.", "Touch of the cornea provokes an involuntary reflex to close the eyelid.", "It refract most of the light that enters the eye."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie St. Elmos Fire, Martin Balsam played the father of the character Leslie Hunter.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Killers was a film based on a short story written by Ernest Hemingway, which starred Burt Lancaster and Ava Gardner.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Hoosiers, the best basketball player in town hasnt played since his old coach died. He steps up for Coach Dale, saves Coach Dales job, and joins the team. What is his name?", "correct_answer": "Jimmy Chitwood", "incorrect_answers": ["James Henrywood", "James Arrowood", "Jimmy Tipwood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jennifer Aniston starred alongside this actor in the 2006 romantic comedy drama The Break-Up.", "correct_answer": "Vince Vaughn", "incorrect_answers": ["Paul Rudd", "Ron Livingston", "Gary Cole"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Roy C Sullivan survived this number of lighting strikes.", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "3", "47"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Cobra is at the top of the food chain, with only two main predators -- one is man and the other is this animal.", "correct_answer": "Mongoose", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackal", "Lynx", "Eagle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Denim, the fabric of which classic blue jeans are sewn, is actually made from what?", "correct_answer": "Cotton", "incorrect_answers": ["Viscose", "Silk", "Wool"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is typical for the Rainforest trees and cannot be seen in trees at higher latitudes?", "correct_answer": "Cauliflory", "incorrect_answers": ["Large leaves", "Fleshy fruits", "Thin bark"]}]